Courtney Regensburger

Cell: (513) 368 - 2670

courtneyregensburger@yahoo.com

https://www.linkedin.com/pub/courtney-regensburger/7a/a00/55

https://github.com/Cregensburger http://cregensburger.github.io/

Profile

Over the past three months, I have attended the programming bootcamp, General Assembly. In that time, I have learned a full-stack set of skills and utilized them on various projects. I have a strong interest in games and front-end design. As such, I have been enhancing my knowledge by teaching myself how to use Unity. I have also been supplementing in-class lessons with courses on Code Academy and Team Treehouse while working on a number of side projects. At this time, I am teaching myself how to create personalized WordPress themes.

Programming Experience

General Assembly, Web Development Immersive, Austin, Texas, 4/27/2015 - 7/23/2015

Tic Tac Toe

My first project. We were given four days to create a fully functional tic tac toe app. As it was a solo project, I wrote all of the code. In this project, I used jQuery for the game logic, using HTML and CSS for the styling. I supplemented the styling by using the tool, Skeleton, which was something I had never used before.

Link: http://guard-kangaroo-36074.bitballoon.com/
Github link: https://github.com/Cregensburger/tic-tac-toe

App-etite

Allowed to come up with our own idea for an application, we opted to make a Rails app that allowed people to post where they wanted to go to lunch and vote. Using such tools as Decrypt and Bootstrap, we were able to implement a new number of features into it. In this project, I was primarily tasked with front end user experience responsibilities.

Link: https://limitless-lake-1270.herokuapp.com/ Github link: https://github.com/James527/app-etite

Hangman

Provided with the CSS and HTML, my partner and I were given eight hours to code a functioning Hangman game application. We succeeded, mostly using JavaScript.

Link: http://movie-title-hangman.bitballoon.com/

Github link: https://github.com/Cregensburger/hangmanProject

Education

General Assembly — Austin, Texas

Web Development Immersive Course, 2015

University of Dayton - Dayton, Ohio

Bachelor of Arts English Literature, 2008 - 2012

Skills

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, Ruby on Rails, Bootstrap, Skeleton, SQL, NoSQL, MongoDB, Node.js and AJAX.

Work Experience

Senior Cheese Clerk, Jungle Jim's International Market

Cincinnati, Ohio - 2/23/2014 - 4/20/2015

My primary purpose was to prepare top-quality products, while maintaining a wealth of information about each cheese and meat we handled. This included general information,

history, uses and possible recipes. It required me to learn quickly and recall a large amount of information in a short period of time. Further improved upon my customer service abilities, including conflict management. Entrusted to train new hires for Production and Floor responsibilities. Given responsibility over designing new displays for the floor.

```
Office Assistant, Wood & Lamping, LLP. Cincinnati, Ohio — 3/18/2014 - 4/20/2015
```

Tasked with filing closed case files, updated and maintained open case files. Experienced in a number of legal secretarial tasks, including such duties as closing case files and updating ongoing client files.

```
Produce Clerk, Kroger, Inc.
Cincinnati, Ohio – 6/25/2013 - 9/10/2013
```

Tasked with maintaining optimal quality of foods, primarily fresh fruit, at the largest Kroger Grocery in the United States. Learned the basics of good customer service and time management within a fast-paced workplace environment.

```
Senior Office Assistant, University of Dayton
Dayton, Ohio – 8/18/2008 - 5/10/2012
```

Number of office responsibilities including, but not limited to: updating and maintaining information databases, coordinating information backup and retrieval, delivery of key documents between organizations, and assisting in the preparation for RISE (Redefining Investment Strategy Education), the largest student run forum on Investment in the United States. Developed strong organization, prioritization, and time management skills. Highly skilled in the use of Microsoft Office 2007 and utilizing various search engines.